{
    "subject": "resource/Truckin'_Magazine",
    "predicate": "property/website",
    "object": "http://www.truckinweb.com/",
    "human_readable": "The website of Truckin' Magazine is http://www.truckinweb.com/.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9504523873329163,
            "question": "What is the URL of Truckin' Magazine's website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9461268782615662,
            "question": "What type of publication is associated with the URL http://www.truckinweb.com/?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.923755407333374,
            "question": "Can you access information about trucks at http://www.truckinweb.com/?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9204840064048767,
            "question": "What is the web address for Truckin' Magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8879536390304565,
            "question": "Where can you find online content from Truckin' Magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8866793513298035,
            "question": "What is the domain name of Truckin' Magazine's website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8301578164100647,
            "question": "Which website provides information about trucks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7310466170310974,
            "question": "Is Truckin' Magazine a digital publication?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6308795809745789,
            "question": "Is there a website dedicated to truck enthusiasts and industry news?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5818164348602295,
            "question": "If you want to read about trucks online, what website should you visit?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The website of Truckin' Magazine is http://www.truckinweb.com/.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1988_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a website dedicated to truck enthusiasts and industry news?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1988_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Truckin' Magazine a digital publication?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1988_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which website provides information about trucks?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1988_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1988_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1988_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1988_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1988_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1988_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1988_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1988_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1988_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1988_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1988_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text excerpts about TRUCKIN' magazine do not mention a specific website address for the publication.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not contain any information about the website of TRUCKIN' Magazine. Therefore, the statement that the website of TRUCKIN' Magazine is <http://www.truckinweb.com/> cannot be verified from the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}